asiasociety.org 2019-06-30

# Website Privacy Statement | Asia Society

General Data Protection Regulation | Anonymous Information | Personally Identifiable Information | Cookies | Google Analytics | Communications Sent to You | Sharing Information with Third Parties | Forums, Bulletin Boards and Chat Rooms | Children Under Age 13 Who Use Our Site | Review and Correction of Personal Data | Security | Location of Servers and Transfer of Information to the United States | Links to Third Parties | Comments and Questions | Your California Privacy Rights

* * *

## Asia Society Website Privacy Statement

The Asia Society last amended this Privacy Statement ("Statement") on May 25, 2018.

* * *

This Statement describes how the Asia Society collects and uses information from our websites' visitors, including Asia Society members. This Statement applies to the websites we control and which are accessible via the following domains: asiasociety.org, asiasociety.net, asiasociety.com, asiastore.org, asiasource.org, askasia.org, asiasocietymuseum.org, asiafood.org, asiainnyc.org, asiasocietysocal.org and internationaled.org (collectively, "Our Site"). This Statement does not apply to any other web pages or websites.

By using Our Site, you consent to our collection and use of information about you in accordance with this Statement. We may change this Statement by occasionally posting an updated version of it on this page. If we decide that it is appropriate, we may also post a notice of the update on Our Site's home page at <http://www.asiasociety.org/>. By continuing to use Our Site after we have posted any changes, you agree to the terms of the updated Statement. This Statement is part of the Terms that govern your use of Our Site, so please read the entire Terms.

We collect two kinds of information from Our Site's visitors: anonymous information and personally identifiable information.

* * *

### Updates Related to the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

The General Data Protection Regulation takes effect as of May 25, 2018, across the European Union. It is designed to offer increased privacy protection, giving individuals stronger and more consistent rights to access and control their personal information. Given the cross-border nature of so many of our transactions today, Asia Society is currently reviewing our policies to ensure they are in compliance with the new regulation. We have put together a cross-organization team to assess our GDPR readiness, identify any gaps and create and implement any changes required to our policies.

Asia Society takes the protection of your personal information seriously. We already have a strong and protective privacy program in place. However in light of the new regulation, we are currently conducting an information audit to review all the ways we collect personal information, reviewing our consent mechanisms to be sure that you understand what you’re granting us and why and how we use it, and evaluating our agreements with the third parties who process some of your personal information to ensure they/we are GDPR compliant.  

We will post an updated privacy policy on our website within the next few weeks. In the meantime if you have any questions, you can contact [webmaster@asiasociety.org](mailto:webmaster@asiasociety.org).

* * *

### Anonymous Information

Our servers automatically log certain information that does not personally identify you ("Anonymous Information"). We use this Anonymous Information in aggregate form to help us manage and improve Our Site. The Anonymous Information we record includes, for example, the pages you visit on our Site, the amount of time you spend viewing those pages, the links and advertisements you click, the browser you use, the address of the web page that referred you to Our Site, and your Internet Protocol address, which tells us about your location and your connection to the Internet.

We do not link Anonymous Information with personally identifiable information. However, we reserve the right to do so, in our discretion, for safety or security reasons or to comply with the law.

back to top

* * *

### Personally Identifiable Information ("Personal Data")

We also collect personally identifiable information that you voluntarily provide to us through Our Site ("Personal Data"). For example, we collect Personal Data when you fill out a member registration form, sign up for a program or event, subscribe to an email newsletter, purchase something from our store, submit a request for information, complete a survey or make a donation or purchase. The types of Personal Data that we collect include:

  * Name
  * Postal address
  * Email address
  * Telephone number
  * Age
  * Sex
  * Racial or ethnic information
  * Educational background
  * Professional and employment-related information, including salary
  * Financial information, such as credit card numbers
  * Hobbies and special interests
  * Other memberships and affiliations you have

We use Personal Data for the purposes for which you provide it, and for other purposes unless you ask us not to do so, including:

  * To fulfill orders for merchandise in our store
  * To fulfill orders for membership, services or products
  * To manage memberships and other subscriptions to our services
  * To process registrations for events, courses and other activities
  * To facilitate participation in contests or surveys
  * To personalize services provided to Asia Society members and visitors to Our Site
  * To promote our other activities, services or products to you
  * To send communications to you on behalf of other organizations that we believe may be of interest (see more detail below under "Communications Sent to You")

We may also collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us about other people. We use this information only for the purpose for which you originally provide it. For example, if you submit another person's email address in order to have material from Our Site forwarded to them (also known as an "email-a-friend" feature), we do not keep the other person's email address. If you purchase and ship products to someone, we will use this information to fulfill your request but will not send marketing communications to your contacts.

back to top

* * *

### Google Analytics

The Google Analytics features Asia Society has implemented is based on Display Advertising (e.g., Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting).

Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

Asia Society will not facilitate the merging of personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information previously collected from Display Advertising features that is based on the DoubleClick cookie unless you have robust notice of, and the user's prior affirmative (i.e., opt-in) consent to, that merger.

If you wish to hide all of your browsing behavior you can use [Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). 

back to top

* * *

### Cookies

Some parts of Our Site rely on cookies, which are small data files placed on your computer. We use cookies only to improve your browsing experience. For example, Our Site's cookies allow you to return to a web-based form that you left partially completed without having to fill in the form from scratch. We do not use cookies to track your preferences or your use of Our Site. You can disable the cookies function, or delete existing cookies, through your web browser's options menu.

back to top

* * *

### Communications Sent to You

We distribute newsletters and other communications by email and regular postal mail. We send these communications to you only if you have signed up to receive them or if you have agreed to receive them as part of an Asia Society membership. We may also use your Personal Data to contact you individually if you initiate correspondence with us. For example, if you email us, we may respond using the contact information you provide.

From time to time, we may use your Personal Data to allow other organizations to send communications that may be of interest to you. We (or our agents) send these mailings on behalf of the other organization, which does not have access to your Personal Data at any time. We exclude our database of Asia Society members from these mailings.

If you no longer wish to receive one or more types of communications, we will happily honor your request. To unsubscribe, simply follow the instructions we include in the mailings we send you, such as the "unsubscribe" link you will find in our email messages. You may also submit your requests to [webmaster@asiasociety.org](mailto:webmaster@asiasociety.org) or Asia Society, Attn: Online Privacy, 725 Park Avenue, New York, New York 10021.

back to top

* * *

### Sharing Information with Third Parties

We do not share, transfer or release Personal Data to third parties besides the contractors who provide us with services necessary to our operations (“Service Providers”). Our Service Providers help us with, for example, web hosting, order fulfillment, subscription management, conference registrations, survey administration, software development, database maintenance, website consulting and credit card processing. These Service Providers may have access to your Personal Data.

In addition, we may occasionally refer you to a Service Provider’s site for help in serving you. For example, we may link you to a Service Provider’s site to process a conference or program registration, to take an order for special Asia Society publications or to gather survey responses. When you follow a referral or a link away from Our Site, you leave Our Site.  This Statement applies only to Our Site, and not to our Service Providers’ sites. You should review their privacy statements to find out how they protect your privacy. 

Finally, we reserve the right to disclose and use Personal Data for necessary purposes, including: to protect our proprietary rights; to protect the safety of customers, employees or property; to carry out a sale or transfer of some or all of our assets; or when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so.

back to top

* * *

### Forums, Bulletin Boards and Chat Rooms

Our Site includes forums, bulletin boards and chat rooms (collectively, “Forums”) that allow you to communicate with other participants in selected Asia Society activities. We frequently use passwords to limit access to the Forums to each activity’s participants. However, your posts to the Forums are not private or confidential. You should consider all material you submit to the Forums to be public.

back to top

* * *

### Children Under Age 13 Who Use Our Site

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information via Our Site from anyone under 13 years of age, unless it is necessary to respond to a one-time request. Once the request has been answered, we will delete the requesting child's personally identifiable information. If you are a parent or guardian and you believe that your child under age 13 may have provided personally identifiable information to us through Our Site, please contact us at [webmaster@asiasociety.org](mailto:webmaster@asiasoc.org) or Asia Society, Attn: Online Privacy, 725 Park Avenue, New York, New York 10021.

back to top

* * *

### Review and Correction of Personal Data

If you would like to review, correct or delete your Personal Data, you can write to us [webmaster@asiasociety.org](mailto:webmaster@asiasoc.org) or Asia Society, Attn: Online Privacy, 725 Park Avenue, New York, New York 10021.

back to top

* * *

### Security

When Our Site uses online forms to collect sensitive Personal Data like credit card numbers, we secure the form with Secure Socket Layers (“SSL”) encryption, one of the most widely accepted and tested forms of data encryption. With less sensitive Personal Data, we use password protection. We also take the following precautions with your Personal Data and other information:

  * Firewalls
  * Software to detect viruses and other intrusions into Our Site and computers
  * Secure hosting environment for our web servers
  * Storage of Personal Data on password-protected computers
  * Restricting access to Personal Data to necessary Asia Society staff

Of course, no mechanism can guarantee that information storage or transmission over the Internet is perfectly safe. We make no warranty, guarantee or representation that Our Site is protected from viruses, security threats or other vulnerabilities or that your Personal Data is always secure. Accordingly, you provide us with your Personal Data at your own risk. 

back to top

* * *

### Location of Servers and Transfer of Information to the United States

Our servers are located in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please note that your Personal Data will be transferred to and stored on a server located in the United States. By submitting your Personal Data to us, you consent to this transfer and to the collection, storage, processing and use of Your Data in the United States.

back to top

* * *

### Links to Third Parties

Solely for your convenience, Our Site contains links to third-party websites and content providers which may interest you. If you follow any link to a third-party site, you leave Our Site. You should review those sites’ privacy statements to find out how they protect your privacy.

back to top

* * *

### Comments and Questions

To request a clarification of this Statement or to send comments about it, please contact us at [webmaster@asiasociety.org](mailto:webmaster@asiasoc.org).

back to top

* * *

### Your California Privacy Rights

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers, members and visitors to Our Site who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at [webmaster@asiasociety.org](mailto:webmaster@asiasoc.org) or Asia Society, Attn: Online Privacy, 725 Park Avenue, New York, New York 10021.

back to top
